♫ I think I'm ready to do my thing ♫
♫ اظن انى مستعد لأمارس ما أتقنه ♫
♫ I think I'm ready to take my chances ♫
♫ أظن انى مستعد لأجرب حظى ♫
♫ I've been dining out and all stressed out ♫
♫ كنت أتعشى بالخارج، ومتوتر للغاية ♫
♫ Due to the circumstances. See? ♫
♫ نظراً للظروف. أترى؟ ♫
♫ I gotta get up, get up, get up, get up ♫
♫ يجب أن انهض، انهض، انهض، انهض ♫
♫ Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up ♫
♫ استيقظ، استيقظ، استيقظ، استيقظ ♫
♫ I see what you're saying ♫
♫ أفهم ما تقوله ♫
♫ We sent a demo to the world, they said it sounds like Take 6 ♫
♫ قمنا بعرض تجربة للعالم، وقالوا اننا نشبه فريق "تيك6" ♫
♫ I said "Hold on, wait a minute, I'll be back with the remix" ♫
♫" قلت " انتظروا دقيقة، وسآتيكم بتوزيع جديد♫
♫ They looking at us funny, we can't make any money ♫
♫ ينظرون الينا بسخرية، ولا نربح أية أموال ♫
♫ It took us years to figure out that we was dealing with dummies ♫
♫ قضينا سنوات لنعرف اننا نتعامل مع أغبياء ♫
♫ They didn't understand the sound from the Bronx, that's the boogie down ♫
♫ لم يفهموا أصوات مدينة "برونكس"، هذا عنها ♫
♫ to Huntsville, Alabama, there's no circles in my planner, so ♫
♫ الى مدينة "هانتسفيل" و "ألاباما"، لم يكن هناك علاقات بخطتى، لذا ♫
♫ It was time to make the product, so we hooked up with Townsend ♫
♫ قد حان الوقت لانتاج عمل، لذا تعاقدنا مع "تاونسيند" ♫
♫ Made a deal with John Neal, on the road sold ten thousand ♫
♫ وعقدنا صفقة مع "جون نيل"، ومع الوقت بعنا 10 آلاف نسخة ♫
♫ WBA, that means a trip to Nashville ♫
♫ وهذا يعنى رحلة الى "ناشفيل"♫
♫ Festplatte showed up and said them boys are naturals ♫
♫ "فيستبلايت" ظهرت وقالت هؤلاء الأولاد طبيعيون ♫
♫ Can you hear what they were hearing? See what they were seeing? ♫
♫ أيمكنك سماع ما كانوا يسمعونه؟ ورؤية ما كانوا يرونه؟ ♫
♫ From Bronx to Berlin, we took the tour European ♫
♫ من مدينة "برونكس" الى "بيرلين"، ذهبنا فى رحلة أوروبية ♫
♫ All vocal yeah, we widit, call the album "What is it?" ♫
♫" كل الأصوات تقول نحن معهم، وسمّوا الألبوم "ما هذا؟ ♫
♫ With Sarah Connor, set the goal for number one and we hit it ♫
♫ ومع "سارة كونور" كان هدفنا أن نكون رقم واحد وفعلناها ♫
♫ But now it's Kev, Sim, Drew, Stew, time for a new day ♫
♫ لكن الآن انهم "كيف"، "سيم"، "درو" و "ستو". انها صفحة جديدة ♫
♫ Ring the alarm, hit 'em on Skype or a two-way ♫
♫ اضرب صفارة الانذار، غنّى لهم على برنامج "سكايب" أو "تو واى" ♫
♫ Sung by the words, we ready to fly! ♫
♫ وسنغنى كما تقول الكلمات، نحن مستعدون للطيران ♫
♫ Fly baby! Time to leave that nest ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! حان وقت ترك العش ♫
♫ Fly baby! This ain't no time to rest ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! لا يوجد وقت للاسترخاء ♫
♫ Come on fly baby, we got work to do ♫
♫ هيا طِر يا صديقى! أمامنا ما نفعله ♫
♫ Here we go, spread my wings and ... ♫
♫... هيا بنا، نفرد أجنحتنا و ♫
♫ Fly baby! Time to leave that nest ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! حان وقت ترك العش ♫
♫ Fly baby! This ain't no time to rest. Come on ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! لا يوجد وقت للاسترخاء. هيا ♫
♫ Fly baby! We got work to do ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! أمامنا ما نفعله ♫
♫ Here we go. Spread my wings and fly. One more time ♫
♫ هيا بنا، نفرد أجنحتنا ونطير. مرة أخرى ♫
♫ Fly baby! Time to leave that nest ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! حان وقت ترك العش ♫
♫ Fly baby! This ain't no time to rest ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! لا يوجد وقت للاسترخاء ♫
♫ Fly baby! We got work to do ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! أمامنا ما نفعله ♫
♫ Here we go, spread my wings and ... ♫
♫... هيا بنا، نفرد أجنحتنا و ♫
♫ Fly baby! Fly baby fly ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! طِر يا صديقى طِر ♫
♫ Fly baby! Fly baby high ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! طِر لأعلى ♫
♫ Fly baby! Up to the sky ♫
♫ طِر يا صديقى! بالسماء♫
♫ Spread my wings and fly ♫
♫ نفرد أجنحتنا ونطير ♫
Instrumental!
آلات موسيقية
♫ We're ready to fly! ♫
♫ نحن مستعدون للطيران ♫
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Thank you very much.
شكرا جزيلا لكم